citing the danger to both drivers and pedestrians...
并提醒司机和行人注意安全…
Not from around here. European design?
不是本地风格 欧式喷漆吗？
Sure it's pretty. Too pretty.
的确很漂亮 但是过头了
Big mistake.
你犯了个大错
Oh... dude.
噢…伙计
You scratch my paint,
你刮我的漆
I scratch yours.
我要你的命
Hey, cherry moped.
嘿 这不是女式轻骑么
Uh, this moped has dual carbs and can go 0 to 60 in 3.5 seconds.
呃 这款轻骑配有双化油器 百公里加速只要3.5秒
Uh, Jack,
呃 杰克
a lady's vital stats are her own business.
女士的属性可是个人隐私
Hey! Nick, right?
嘿！你叫尼克对吧？
Actually... it's Jack.
其实…是杰克
Jack. Sorry. I am Sierra.
杰克 不好意思 我叫塞拉
I... I know.
我…我知道
You once offered to take me for a ride?
你说过要带我去兜风的是吗？
Of... course I did, at any time.
我…当然说过 随时恭候
I'm your guardian, kiddo.
我是你的保镖 小鬼
Not your wingman.
不是电灯泡
So, how about now?
那么 现在如何？
Uh...
呃…
Hey, small world.
嘿 世界真小啊
Em... been having a conversation.
呃…我们在聊天
Cheer captain here might enjoy watching you take on four wheels of muscle car.
这位啦啦队长可能很乐意欣赏 你和四轮肌肉车过招
Are you challenging me... to a race?
你是想跟我…赛车吗？
You catch on quick, paunch. What do you say?
理解力不错嘛 笨鸟 敢不敢应战？
Uh...
呃…
You... you didn't let me answer.
你…你没让我回答
Nope.
对
Arcee, we can smoke him.
阿尔茜 我们可以赢得他灰头土脸
Yeape.
没错
Uh... you just don't get it.
呃…你真不近人情
I don't make the rules, Jack.
规矩不是我定的 杰克
Optumis does.
是擎天柱
And rule No.1, in case you missed it,
守则第一条还记得不
never abuse power for a personal game.
绝不能在个人享乐上滥用能力
And that includes horse power.
也包括马力
Vince, maybe racing isn't such a good idea.
文斯 赛车可能不太适合我
hahaha, figured.
明白
You ride around like your bike's something special.
你把摩托车当成宝贝一样骑
But it's just a chunky clunky trike, and ugly.
可它只是辆笨蛋老破车 丑到极点了！
That's it. The yahoo is going down.
够了 这小丑死定了
Wow, what happened to rule No.1?
喔 守则第一条不管了？
Gets bent. Just this once.
守则也是人定的 下不为例
Yo, girls, your pal Darby, he's...
我说姑娘们 你们那个姓达比的 他…
Ready when you are, Vinny.
随时应战 小蚊子
Dirt road by Trucker's Ranch. One hour.
司机农场旁边的土道 一小时后
From here to the next mile marker. Ready? Go.
从这儿到下一个里程牌 预备…出发！
Oh, that was fair.
还真公平啊
Eh... Arcee?
呃…阿尔茜？
Winning isn't enough, Jack.
只是A就便宜他了 杰克
You wanna make him cry.
要让他欲哭无泪
What?
什么？
Outstanding!
一马当先！
Oh, hey, now it might be a good time to offer Sierra quick once around the block?
喔 嘿 现在可不可以顺势带塞拉在街上兜一圈？
Don't push it.
别得寸进尺
Ah, Breakdown,
啊 打击
has there been any change in Megatron's condition?
威震天的身体状况有点起色没有？
Um, only cosmetic.
呃 只是脸色好了点
Well, I am sure that you and the good doctor have been doing everything in your power.
好吧 我相信你和那个神医已经尽力了
Where is Knock Out?
击倒哪儿去了？
Can you believe what some skinjob did to me?
你能猜到某个臭皮匠对我做了什么吗？
You have been street racing among the humans again, haven't you?
你又去和人类飙车了 对不对？
I'm not only an automobile, I am an automobile enthusiast.
我不只是辆车 还是辆狂热的赛车
I do strive to run a tight ship, Knock Out.
我力求军纪严明 击倒
I would strongly suggest that you seek my permission next time you decide to disappear on one of your little jobs.
我强烈建议你 下次你决定开小差的时候 要征得本人的许可
No worries, Herr Commandant.
没问题 指挥官先生
It is lord to you.
你应该叫陛下
Only if Megatron takes a nosedive.
等威震天驾崩之后再说吧
The day our master emerges from stasis,
有朝一日我们的主人苏醒
I will graciously relinquish the title.
我将把头衔拱手相让
But I believe that outcome is unlikely.
但我认为几乎没这个可能
Something to do with the quality of medical care around here.
目前的医疗水平不过如此
So continue buffing.
继续抛光吧
We do want Megatron looking his best for the memorial.
我们真心希望威震天在追悼会上红光满面
Buff this.
先给我抛个光
Not a word to anyone.
别告诉任何人
Our little secret.
我们的小秘密
Dude! vong... and the winner is?
伙计！嗡 嗡 嗡…获胜者是…
Miko, who told you?
神子 谁告诉你的？
You kidding? It's all over school!
你开玩笑吧？全校都知道了！
You beat the pants off that blowhard bully Vince.
你让那个叫文斯的学校霸王输得找不着北了
You guys have to keep this on the DL, especially from Optimus.
你们得严格保密 尤其不能告诉擎天柱
Hey, I've been looking for you.
嘿 我正找你呢
The race, how great was that, I was like...
那比赛可真过瘾 我一直在喊…
Yeah, go Jack!
耶！加油 杰克！
It... it was no big deal.
也…没什么
You got that right.
算你说对了
If you think you can run with the big boys,
如果你觉得能跑过那些高手的话？
the circuit, tonight, 11pm.
今晚11点 赛道见
You agreed to what?
你答应了？
It was some kind of secret racing club.
那是个地下赛车俱乐部
But I don't know, I had no choice.
我也不清楚 我没得选
Sierra was standing right there.
塞拉当时就在我旁边
You always have a choice, Jack.
你总会有选择权的 杰克
And what part of "just this once" did you not understand?
你听不懂什么叫“下不为例”吗？
I know... I'm sorry.
我知道…对不起
But... we are on, right?
可…我们会去的 对吗？
We are not on.
我们不去
Knok Out, Starsceam's been looking for you again,
击倒 红蜘蛛又找不着你了
where did you go?
你在哪儿？
Out for a little drive.
自然是出来兜风了
I just rode from town to town,
在几个城市之间转转
sniffing around until...
侦察侦察…
the next opportunity presents itself.
机会总是能找上门来的
Raf,
拉夫
uh... is there anyway I could borrow Bumblebee for one hour?
呃…可以把大黄蜂借我一个小时吗？
Jack, you know racing is against the rules.
杰克 赛车违反规定 你是知道的
What if Optimus found out?
擎天柱知道了怎么办？
But Raf, he's gotta get the girl,
但是拉夫 他得去泡妞
and beat the bully...
顺便打黑除恶…
Well...
那…
Come on, Raf, just this once...
求你了 拉夫 下不为例…
Bike is in the shop.
摩托车送修了
Circuit drivers, are you ready?
各位车手 准备好了吗？
Make it beep but keep it clean!
开足马力 但要遵守规则
Fire on 5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
准备 5 4 3 2 1！
The Autobot they called... Bumblebee.
那个汽车人叫…大黄蜂
What was that, Bee?
那是什么 小蜂？
Wait, I know that car.
慢着 我认识那车
What the...
什么…
Can you lose it, Bee?
你能甩掉他吗 小蜂？
What do you say?
你说什么？
I hope that means yes.
但愿那是“同意”的意思
Cause I'd rather not have to call base for backup.
我可不想呼叫基地请求增援
Anyone's seen Jack?
有谁看到杰克了吗?
Not since...
上次之后…
we last saw him.
就再没见过
They are racing, aren't they?
他们在赛车 对吧？
Just this once.
下不为例
Did you know about this?
你知情吗？
No... maybe. A little.
不…大概 知道一点
You are being chased by Knock Out?
你们被击倒盯上了？
That sounds like a Decepticon.
听上去像是个霸天虎
Bee, do not engage.
小蜂 不要交战
Your first priority is to keep Jack safe.
你的首要任务是保证杰克的安全
Until I get my hands on him.
到时候我再教训他
Slick.
小心 地滑
I think we lost him, Bee.
我们大概甩掉他了 小蜂
Oh, you gotta be kidding me!
喔 别开这种玩笑啊！
Darby!
达比！
Vince, you have to get out of here, you win, okay?
文斯 你得离开这儿 算你赢了 行吗？
Congratulations! Now, go!
恭喜你！快走！
No, no, start or backoff, loser,
不 不 言出必行 笨蛋
we are finishing this race!
必须跑完比赛！
Don't wanna take to the finish line? Fine!
不想在终点线出丑是吗？行！
Then we got something to settle right here! Right now!
那我们就地解决！
What's going on? What are you...
怎么回事？你要干…
Breakdown, you'll never guess what I'm packing -
打击 你绝对想不到我抓到了什么
Bumblebee's human friend.
是大黄蜂的人类伙伴
And, when the Autobot attempts to stage a rescue...
等那个汽车人来营救的时候…
He has a... Breakdown.
就给他来个致命“打击”
Bee, he's getting away!
小蜂 他跑了！
I... I can't understand you!
我…我听不懂你的话！
Look, I am not Raf,
听着 我可不是拉夫
can't you just... honk once for bad news,
你能不能…鸣笛一声代表坏消息
and honk twice for good news?
两声代表好消息？
Jack, we need to have a little chat.
杰克 我们得好好谈谈
Later, Arcee.
等等吧 阿尔茜
Vince's got snatched by the slick sportscar Con.
文斯被那个狡猾的跑车虎子抓走了
What would Knock Out want with a random human?
击倒怎么会抓个无名氏呢？
He probably mistook Vince for Bumblebee's human friend.
也许他把文斯当成大黄蜂的人类伙伴了
I'm not even Bumblebee's human friend.
可连我都不算是大黄蜂的人类伙伴
I don't know, it doesn't matter why he took him... Vince is in trouble!
我不知道 管他为什么抓人 文斯有麻烦了！
Oh well, tough break for Vince.
好吧 算文斯倒霉
Bulkhead!
隔板！
Why, I heard this guy is a jerk.
怎么了 这家伙不是个混蛋吗？
No arguement there, but the guy is also innocent.
我不否认 但他是无辜的
Vince doesn't deserve to get crushed by Cons.
文斯不该被虎子蹂躏
Hop on.
上车
They should have called off by now.
他们早该回来了
You think Bumblebee is okay?
你觉得大黄蜂会有事吗？
Don't worry, Raf,
别担心 拉夫
Bulkhead won't let anything happen to Jack or Bee.
隔板不会让杰克和小蜂出事的
We should just tell Optimus the truth.
我们应该跟擎天柱说实话
Absolutely not.
绝对不行
We made a deal.
我们说好的
Just act completely normal.
假装没事就行
Raf, Miko,
拉夫 神子
do either of you know where the others have gone?
你们知道其他人去哪儿了吗？
Why, no, sir. We do not know.
什么？不 长官 我们不知道
Miko is correct. We do not know.
神子说得对 我们不知道
Why would we know?
我们怎么会知道？
Hum...
呃…
Bumblebee brought company.
大黄蜂叫帮手来了
On your guard, boys, could be a trap.
提高警惕 各位 可能是个陷阱
Remember, no shooting.
记住 别开火
Speaking of safety,
安全起见
here is where you get off.
你该在这儿下车
Hmm... Where's the two-wheeler?
那个两轮儿的去哪儿了？
Hey! Watch the paint!
嘿！当心我的喷漆！
That's my girl.
好姑娘！
Uh... Breakdown,
呃 打击
in case you are looking for me, thing's got messy.
友情提醒你一下 场面有点乱
So I hit the road.
我开溜了
One scrape is enough for today.
一天剐蹭一次已经受够了
Eat my dust.
吃灰去吧
Optimus, Knock Out has a hostage.
擎天柱 击倒有人质
Understood.
明白
Do you know how hard that is to replace?
你知道换零件多麻烦吗？
Optimus... This was my fault.
擎天柱…是我的错
We must get this boy to safety immediately.
必须立刻把这男孩带到安全地区
Explanations can come later, from all of you.
认错另选时间 你们都有责任
How did... What happened?
怎么了…出什么事了？
Someguys... jumped you under the bridge,
有人在桥下抓住你
they tossed you into their trunk,
想拉你入伙
must be some kind of initiation.
像是某种入会仪式
Really?
真的吗？
Yeah, I found you...
没错 我发现你…
knocked out by the side of the road.
晕倒在路边
I... I gotta be honest, after what I saw tonight,
我…得承认 有了今晚的经历
I'm thinking racing just isn't my thing.
我觉得赛车真的不适合我
I hear you, Darby,
这还用说 达比
hard to win a race driving a pedal car.
骑脚踏车是赢不了比赛的
Knock Out! Was I not clear?
击倒！我说的还不清楚吗？
You have defied my order yet again.
你竟敢再次无视我的命令！
My mistake, commander Starscream.
我知错了 红蜘蛛指挥官
But I've learned my lesson.
我也吸取了教训
And paid the price.
还付出了代价
It is Lord!
叫我陛下！
And you have paid when I say you have paid.
而且你付出多少代价 由我说了算
Do not worry, Your punishment shall be mearly... cosmetic.
别担心 对你的惩罚只是…面子问题
No... not the finish, anything but the finish, No!!
不 别刮喷漆 除了喷漆什么都行 不！！
So, Jack, do you have time for that ride?
那个…杰克 你有时间去兜风吗？
Uh... I... I'm sorry, Sierra, I can't right now.
呃 我…很抱歉 塞拉 现在不行
No problem, I guess I'll just see you around.
没关系 那我们就…回头见吧
Hop on.
上车
Oh... Really?
喔…真的吗？
Just this once.
下不为例